A Guide to the Trilateral Commission (North America) records FA420
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Officer's Files, 1974-1998; 5; 38.43 Cubic Feet 69 letter document boxes, 12 legal document boxes, and 5 record storage boxes.
  - Charles B. Heck, 5.3
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1986 April (Box 282, Folder 2893)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1986 May (Box 282, Folder 2894)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1986 May (Box 282, Folder 2895)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1986 June (Box 282, Folder 2896)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1986 July (Box 283, Folder 2897)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1986 August (Box 283, Folder 2898)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1986 September (Box 283, Folder 2899)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1986 October (Box 284, Folder 2900)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1986 November (Box 284, Folder 2901)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1986 December (Box 284, Folder 2902)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1987 January (Box 285, Folder 2903)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1987 March (Box 285, Folder 2904)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1987 April (Box 285, Folder 2905)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1987 May (Box 286, Folder 2906)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1987 June (Box 286, Folder 2907)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1987 July (Box 286, Folder 2908)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1987 August (Box 286, Folder 2909)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1987 September (Box 286, Folder 2910)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1987 October (Box 286, Folder 2911)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1987 November (Box 286A, Folder 3968)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1987 December (Box 286A, Folder 3969)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1991 January (Box 286A, Folder 3970)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1991 February (Box 286A, Folder 3971)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1991 March (Box 286A, Folder 3972)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1991 April (Box 286A, Folder 3973)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1991 May (Box 286A, Folder 3974)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1991 June (Box 286A, Folder 3975)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Projects - Environmental Project, 1990 (Box 286A, Folder 3976)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Projects (Box 286A, Folder 3977)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1988 January (Box 287, Folder 2912)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1988 February (Box 287, Folder 2913)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1988 March (Box 287, Folder 2914)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1988 April (Box 287, Folder 2915)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1988 May (Box 287, Folder 2916)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1988 June (Box 288, Folder 2917)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1988 July (Box 288, Folder 2918)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1988 August (Box 288, Folder 2919)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1988 September (Box 288, Folder 2920)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1988 September (Box 288, Folder 2921)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1988 September (Box 288, Folder 2922)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1988 October (Box 288, Folder 2923)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1988 November (Box 288, Folder 2924)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1988 November (Box 288, Folder 2925)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1988 December (Box 289, Folder 2926)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1989 January (Box 289, Folder 2927)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1989 February (Box 289, Folder 2928)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1989 March (Box 289, Folder 2929)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1989 April (Box 289, Folder 2930)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1989 May (Box 290, Folder 2931)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1989 June (Box 290, Folder 2932)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1989 July-August (Box 290, Folder 2933)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1989 September (Box 290, Folder 2934)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1989 October (Box 291, Folder 2935)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1989 November (Box 291, Folder 2936)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1989 December (Box 291, Folder 2937)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1990 January (Box 291, Folder 2938)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1990 February (Box 291, Folder 2939)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1990 March (Box 291, Folder 2940)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1990 April (Box 292, Folder 2941)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1990 May (Box 292, Folder 2942)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1990 June (Box 292, Folder 2943)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1990 July (Box 292, Folder 2944)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1990 August (Box 292, Folder 2945)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1990 September (Box 292, Folder 2946)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1990 October (Box 293, Folder 2947)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1990 November (Box 293, Folder 2948)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1990 December (Box 293, Folder 2949)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1997 May (Box 293, Folder 2950)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1997 June-August (Box 293, Folder 2951)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1997 September (Box 293, Folder 2952)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1997 October (Box 293, Folder 2953)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1997 December (Box 294, Folder 2954)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1998 January (Box 294, Folder 2955)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1998 February (Box 294, Folder 2956)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1998 February (Box 294, Folder 2957)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1998 March (Box 294, Folder 2958)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1998 May (Box 294, Folder 2959)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1998 March-June (Box 294, Folder 2960)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1998 July-September (Box 294, Folder 2961)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1998 July (Box 295, Folder 2962)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1998 August (Box 295, Folder 2963)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1998 September-October (Box 295, Folder 2964)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chronological, 1998 November-December (Box 295, Folder 2965)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Meeting, Pocantico - Summary, 1972 July (Box 296, Folder 2966)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Executive Committee, First Meeting, Tokyo, 1973 (Box 296, Folder 2967)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Trustees Minutes, 1973-1977 (Box 296, Folder 2968)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Annual Reports, 1973-1977 (Box 296, Folder 2969)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Principal Meetings List, 1973-1981 (Box 296, Folder 2970)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - North American Meeting, 1973 October 15-16 (Box 296, Folder 2971)
    - Charles B. Heck Files, 1974 (Box 296, Folder 2972)
    - Charles B. Heck Files, 1975 (Box 296, Folder 2973)
    - Charles B. Heck Files, 1976 (Box 296, Folder 2974)
    - Charles B. Heck Files, 1977 (Box 296, Folder 2975)
    - Charles B. Heck Files, 1978 (Box 296, Folder 2976)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Possible Meeting in Developing Country, 1979 (Box 296, Folder 2977)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Atlantic Institute - ?Fair Share?, 1979 (Box 296, Folder 2978)
    - Charles B. Heck Files, 1980 (Box 296, Folder 2979)
    - Charles B. Heck Files, 1981-1982 (Box 296, Folder 2980)
      Includes: European Regional Meeting, Berlin
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chairman, ExComm, Annual Meeting, 1982 (Box 297, Folder 2981)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Possible New Task Force Topics (Box 297, Folder 2982)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Future of the Commission, 1983 (Box 297, Folder 2983)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Future of the Commission, 1983 (Box 297, Folder 2983A)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Finance Letters, Contributions, 1984 (Box 297, Folder 2984)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Member Responses on Future, 1984 (Box 297, Folder 2985)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Chairmen?s Statements, 1985 (Box 297, Folder 2986)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Speeches, 1985 (Box 297, Folder 2987)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Afternoon Discussions on Second Day, 1985 (Box 297, Folder 2988)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Plenary Meeting, Tokyo - Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 297, Folder 2989)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Plenary Meeting, Rome, 1983 April (Box 298, Folder 2990)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 (Box 298, Folder 2991)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - White House, 1984 (Box 298, Folder 2991A)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Drivers, 1984 (Box 298, Folder 2992)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Speech, Program and List of Participants, 1984 (Box 298, Folder 2993)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Proposed Membership to Council on Foreign Relations (Box 298, Folder 2994)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - European Trip, 1981 Fall (Box 298, Folder 2995)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Meetings, 1974-1981 (Box 299, Folder 2996)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Phone Conversations, Memos, 1975-1976 (Box 299, Folder 2996A)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 299, Folder 2996B)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Washington, D.C. - Interpreters, 1974 (Box 299, Folder 2997)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Joseph Reed (Box 299, Folder 2998)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Bill Martin (Box 299, Folder 2999)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Strategic Air Command Headquarters Trip, 1976 February (Box 299, Folder 3000)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Structural Reform of Commission, 1976 (Box 299, Folder 3001)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Alternatives for Future of TC, 1975 (Box 299, Folder 3002)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Possible TC Merger, 1977 (Box 299, Folder 3003)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Future of CFR as stated by Win Lord, 1977 (Box 299, Folder 3004)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - David Rockefeller Itinerary, 1983 November 11-16 (Box 299, Folder 3005)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - David Rockefeller - Meeting, Washington D.C., 1984 (Box 299, Folder 3005A)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Task Forces, 1986 (Box 299, Folder 3006)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Plenary Meeting, 1984 (Box 300, Folder 3007)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Future of the Commission, 1984 (Box 300, Folder 3008)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Employment Requests, Resumes (Box 300, Folder 3009)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Tadashi Hanami Papers (Box 300, Folder 3010)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Seuo Sekiguchi Papers (Box 300, Folder 3011)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Elke Thiel Papers (Box 300, Folder 3012)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Peter Jenkins April 10 Presentation (Box 300, Folder 3013)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Misc. Papers and Reports, 1978-1982 (Box 300, Folder 3013A)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Masashi Nishihara - Japanese Defense Report, 1980 (Box 300, Folder 3014)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Germany, 1982 (Box 301, Folder 3015)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Hungary, 1982 (Box 301, Folder 3016)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Frank Tugwell, 1980 (Box 301, Folder 3017)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - John Mugno, 1981 (Box 301, Folder 3018)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Japan Clippings, 1978-1979 (Box 301, Folder 3019)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Euro-Communism Embassy Paper (Box 301, Folder 3020)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Hanns Maull, 1975-1981 (Box 301, Folder 3021)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Council on Foreign Relations, 1980-1981 (Box 301, Folder 3022)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Possible Trilateral Research Institute on Foreign Affairs, 1982 (Box 301, Folder 3023)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Olson and Immerman Papers, 1978-1980 (Box 301, Folder 3024)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Henry Owen, 1982 (Box 301, Folder 3025)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Ernesto Vellano, 1981-1982 (Box 301, Folder 3026)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Trilateral Commission - Paris, 1981-1982 (Box 301, Folder 3027)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Trilateral Commission - Tokyo, 1981 (Box 301, Folder 3028)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chairmen, Executive Committee, etc., 1984 (Box 301, Folder 3029)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chairmen, Executive Committee, etc., 1985 (Box 301, Folder 3030)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Annual Reports, 1985-1990 (Box 301, Folder 3031)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chairmen, Executive Committee, etc., 1987 (Box 301, Folder 3032)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Atlantic Institute, 1987-1988 (Box 302, Folder 3033)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Trip to the Soviet Union, 1988 (Box 302, Folder 3034)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chairmen, Executive Committee, etc., 1988 (Box 302, Folder 3035)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chairmen, Executive Committee, etc., 1989 (Box 302, Folder 3036)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Memo - Pub-Distribution, 1989 April 5 (Box 302, Folder 3037)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Plenary Meeting, Mexico City - Discussions, 1990 (Box 302, Folder 3038)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Plenary Meeting, Mexico City - Discussions, 1990 (Box 302, Folder 3039)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Plenary Meeting, Mexico City - Summary, 1990 (Box 302, Folder 3040)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C., - Press, 1990 (Box 303, Folder 3041)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Chairmen, Executive Committee, etc., 1990 (Box 303, Folder 3042)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Plenary Meeting, Washington, D.C. - Questionnaire Responses (Future of TC), 1990 (Box 303, Folder 3043)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Committee on Future, 1990 (Box 303, Folder 3044)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chairmen, Executive Committee, etc., 1991 (Box 303, Folder 3045)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chairmen, Executive Committee, etc., 1992 (Box 303, Folder 3046)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Miscellaneous, 1992 (Box 303, Folder 3047)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chairmen, Executive Committee, etc., 1993 (Box 304, Folder 3048)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Special N.A. Ex Comm/Trustees Meeting, 1993 October (Box 304, Folder 3048A)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Miscellaneous, 1993 (Box 304, Folder 3049)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chairmen, Executive Committee, etc., 1994 (Box 304, Folder 3050)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 304, Folder 3051)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chairmen, Executive Committee, etc., 1995 (Box 304, Folder 3052)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 304, Folder 3053)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chairmen, Executive Committee, etc., 1996 (Box 304, Folder 3054)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Future of Trilateral, 1996 (Box 304, Folder 3055)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 304, Folder 3056)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chairmen, Executive Committee, etc., 1997 (Box 305, Folder 3057)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 305, Folder 3058)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chairmen, Executive Committee, etc., 1998 (Box 305, Folder 3059)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - 25th Anniversary Evening, 1998 (Box 305, Folder 3060)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Canadian 25th Anniversary Evening, 1998 (Box 305, Folder 3061)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 305, Folder 3062)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chairmen, Executive Committee, etc., 1999 (Box 305, Folder 3063)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Other, 1999 (Box 305, Folder 3064)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chairmen, Executive Committee, etc., 2000 (Box 305, Folder 3065)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Tokyo Annual Meeting, 2000 (Box 305, Folder 3066)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Brainstorming Dinner, Tokyo, 2000 (Box 305, Folder 3067)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Other, 2000 (Box 306, Folder 3068)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Website, Shared Databases, 1995-2000 (Box 306, Folder 3069)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Central Asia, 2000 (Box 306, Folder 3070)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Chairmen, Executive Committee, etc., 2001 (Box 306, Folder 3071)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - London Annual Meeting, 2001 (Box 306, Folder 3072)
    - Charles B. Heck Files - Other, 2001 (Box 306, Folder 3073)
  - Assistants to Charles B. Heck, 5.3A
    - Catherine Katin
      Assistant to Heck,1977-
      - CK Reports, Minutes, 1977-1979 (Box 306, Folder 3074)
    - Erna Prickett Adelson
      Assistant to Heck, 1979-1981.
      - EPA Chronological, 1979 August-December (Box 306, Folder 3075)
      - EPA Chronological, 1979 August-December (Box 306, Folder 3076)
      - EPA Chronological, 1980 January-April (Box 306, Folder 3077)
      - EPA Chronological, 1980 (Box 306, Folder 3078)
      - EPA Chronological, 1980 May-August (Box 307, Folder 3079)
      - EPA Chronological, 1980 September-December (Box 307, Folder 3080)
      - EHP Chronological, 1981 (Box 307, Folder 3081)
      - EHP Staff Meeting Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 307, Folder 3082)
      - Memos to EHP, 1981 (Box 307, Folder 3083)
      - EPA Chronological, 1981 January-April (Box 307, Folder 3084)
    - Daniel J. Newman
      Assistant to Heck, 1981-1984.
      - DJN Chronological, 1981 August-December (Box 307, Folder 3085)
      - DJN Chronological, 1982 January-June (Box 307, Folder 3086)
      - DJN Chronological, 1982 July-December (Box 307, Folder 3087)
      - DJN Chronological, 1983 January-June (Box 307, Folder 3088)
      - DJN Chronological, 1983 July-December (Box 307, Folder 3089)
      - Memos to DJN, 1981-1983 (Box 307, Folder 3090)
      - DJN Chronological, 1984 January-June (Box 307, Folder 3091)
  - Christopher Makins, 5.4
    - Christopher J. Makins Chronological Files, 1975 August (Box 307A, Folder 4142)
    - Christopher J. Makins Chronological Files, 1975 September (Box 307A, Folder 4143)
    - Christopher J. Makins Chronological Files, 1975 October (Box 307A, Folder 4144)
    - Christopher J. Makins Chronological Files, 1975 November (Box 307A, Folder 4145)
    - Christopher J. Makins Chronological Files, 1975 December (Box 307A, Folder 4146)
    - Christopher J. Makins Chronological Files, 1976 January (Box 307A, Folder 4147)
    - Christopher J. Makins Chronological Files, 1976 February (Box 307A, Folder 4148)
    - Christopher J. Makins Chronological Files, 1976 March (Box 307A, Folder 4149)
    - Christopher J. Makins Chronological Files, 1976 April (Box 307A, Folder 4150)
    - Christopher J. Makins Chronological Files, 1976 May (Box 307A, Folder 4151)
    - Christopher J. Makins Chronological Files, 1976 June (Box 307A, Folder 4152)
    - Christopher J. Makins - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 307A, Folder 4153)
  - David Rockefeller, 5.5
    - David Rockefeller - Speeches, 1977-1980 (Box 308, Folder 3092)
    - David Rockefeller Chronological Files
    - David Rockefeller Chronological Files, 1985 April-May (Box 308A, Folder 3978)
    - David Rockefeller Chronological Files, 1985 June (Box 308A, Folder 3979)
    - David Rockefeller Chronological Files, 1985 July-September (Box 308A, Folder 3980)
    - David Rockefeller Chronological Files, 1985 October-November (Box 308A, Folder 3981)
    - David Rockefeller Chronological Files, 1985 December (Box 308A, Folder 3982)
    - David Rockefeller Chronological Files, 1986 January-March (Box 308A, Folder 3983)
    - David Rockefeller Chronological Files, 1986 April-June (Box 308A, Folder 3984)
    - David Rockefeller Chronological Files, 1986 July-November (Box 308A, Folder 3985)
    - David Rockefeller Chronological Files, 1986 November-December (Box 308A, Folder 3986)
    - David Rockefeller Chronological Files, 1987 January-September (Box 308A, Folder 3987)
    - David Rockefeller Chronological Files, 1987 November-1988 May (Box 308A, Folder 3988)
    - David Rockefeller Chronological Files, 1988 July-1989 February (Box 308A, Folder 3989)
    - David Rockefeller Chronological Files, 1989 April-October (Box 308A, Folder 3990)
    - David Rockefeller Chronological Files, 1989 November-1990 March (Box 308A, Folder 3991)
    - David Rockefeller Chronological Files, 1990-1991 (Box 308A, Folder 3992)
    - David Rockefeller Chronological Files, 1993-1998 (Box 308A, Folder 3993)
  - Gerard C. Smith, 5.6
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Executive Committee Meeting, Tokyo, 1973 October 20-22 (Box 308B, Folder 3994)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Executive Committee Meeting - Press Coverage, Tokyo, 1973 October 20-22 (Box 308B, Folder 3994A)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Executive Committee Meeting - Communique and Statement of Purpose, Tokyo, 1973 October 20-22 (Box 308B, Folder 3994B)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Executive Committee Meeting, Brussels, 1974 April 4-5 (Box 308B, Folder 3995)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Executive Committee Meeting, Brussels, 1974 June 23-25 (Box 308B, Folder 3996)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Brussels - Joint Communique (Box 308B, Folder 3997)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - N.A. Commissioners, 1974 (Box 308B, Folder 3997A)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Executive Committee Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1974 December (Box 308B, Folder 3998)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Executive Committee Meeting, Washington, D.C., 1974 December (Box 308B, Folder 3998A)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Executive Committee - Resolution, Washington, D.C., 1974 December (Box 308B, Folder 3998B)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - T.C. Meeting, Ottawa/Washington, D.C., 1976 May 9-13 (Box 308C, Folder 3999)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Advisory Council On Japan-U.S. Economic Relations, 1973-1974 (Box 308C, Folder 4000)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - (Proposed) Foreign Policy Article (Box 308C, Folder 4001)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Tripartite Conference, Monte Carlo, 1973 May 21-24 (Box 308C, Folder 4002)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Trilateral Book - Trade Post World War I History (Box 308C, Folder 4003)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Impact Mailings - Newsmen, 1974 (Box 308C, Folder 4004)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Commissioners - Distribution to Commissioners, 1973 (Box 308C, Folder 4005)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Correspondence - General Preliminary, 1972 (Box 308C, Folder 4006)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Progress Report, Program Activity, 1973 (Box 308C, Folder 4007)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Trilateral Tribune, 1974 (Box 308C, Folder 4008)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - General, 1973 (Box 308C, Folder 4009)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Joint Project - Atlantic Council/Atlantic Institute/Japan Society, 1973 (Box 308, Folder 4010)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Battelle, 1976-1977 (Box 308, Folder 4011)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Diebold Article, 1973 (Box 308, Folder 4012)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Paris/London, 1977 March (Box 308, Folder 4013)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Atlantic Institute for International Affairs, 1974-1976 (Box 308, Folder 4014)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Memorandum of Conversations, 1972-1973 (Box 308, Folder 4015)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Staff - Possibilities (Box 308, Folder 4016)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Task Force, 1975-1976 (Box 308, Folder 4017)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - Proposal w/o Financials, 1973-1974 (Box 308, Folder 4018)
    - Gerard C. Smith Files - TC Proposal (Box 308, Folder 4018A)